midgetmomma.com 2019-12-13

# Disclosure/ Disclaimer/ Privacy Policy • MidgetMomma

UPDATED on May 24th, 2018

This blog is a collaborative blog written by a group of individuals. For questions about this blog, please contact [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

We at MidgetMomma.com respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you what personally identifiable information we may collect and how it may be used.

We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you what personally identifiable information we may collect and how it may be used. This statement only applies to this Website.

WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT AND HOW IS IT USED?

**Information You Voluntarily Submit to the Website** : We may collect personal information from you such as your name or email address. For example, you may voluntarily submit information to the Website by leaving a comment, subscribing to a newsletter, or submitting a contact form. In addition, you are able to create a user profile, which allows you to create a username and password. We will store the username, but your password will not be visible in our records.

**Information We Collect from Others** : We may receive information about you from other sources. You may link your Facebook, Instagram, and/or Google accounts to your user profile. If you choose to link your Facebook, Instagram, and/or Google accounts to your user profile, we will receive your name, email address and profile picture associated with that account. The Website utilizes the Facebook commenting system, so if you choose to comment on a Website post, your profile picture will appear.

**Automatically-Collected Information** : We automatically collect certain information about you and the device with which you access the Website. For example, when you use the Website, we will log your IP address, operating system type, browser type, referring website, pages you viewed, and the dates/times when you accessed the Website. We may also collect information about actions you take when using the Website, such as links clicked.

**Cookies** : We may log information using cookies, which are small data files stored on your browser by the Website. We may use both session cookies, which expire when you close your browser, and persistent cookies, which stay on your browser until deleted, to provide you with a more personalized experience on the Website.

HOW YOUR INFORMATION MAY BE USED

We may use the information collected in the following ways:

  * To operate and maintain the Website;
  * To create your account, identify you as a user of the Website, and customize the Website for your account; 
  * To send you promotional information, such as newsletters. Each email promotion will provide information on how to opt-out of future mailings;
  * To send you administrative communications, such as administrative emails, confirmation emails, technical notices, updates on policies, or security alerts;
  * To respond to your comments or inquiries;
  * To provide you with user support;
  * To track and measure advertising on the Website;
  * To protect, investigate, and deter against unauthorized or illegal activity.

THIRD-PARTY USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may share your information with third parties when you explicitly authorize us to share your information.

Additionally, the Website may use third-party service providers to service various aspects of the Website. Each third-party service provider’s use of your personal information is dictated by their respective privacy policies.

The Website currently uses the following third-party service providers:

**Google Analytics** – this service tracks Website usage and provides information such as referring websites and user actions on the Website. Google Analytics may capture your IP address, but no other personal information is captured by Google Analytics.

**ConvertKit** – this service is used for delivery of email updates and newsletters. We store your name and email address for purposes of delivering such communications. If you wish to unsubscribe all you have to do is hit the unsubscribe button in the newsletter and you will be removed from the mailing list. 

At this time, your personal information is not shared with any other third-party applications. This list may be amended from time to time in the Website’s sole discretion.

Except when required by law, we will not sell, distribute, or reveal your email addresses or other personal information without your consent; however, we may disclose or transfer personal information collected through the Website to third parties who acquire all or a portion of our business, which may be the result of a merger, consolidation, or purchase of all or a portion of our assets, or in connection with any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding brought by or against us.

ANONYMOUS DATA

From time to time, we may use anonymous data, which does not identify you alone, or when combined with data from other parties. This type of anonymous data may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Examples of this anonymous data may include analytics or information collected from cookies.

PUBLICLY VISIBLE INFORMATION

If you create a user profile on the Website or leave a comment, certain information may be publicly visible. To create a user profile, you must choose a username and password and input your email address for profile confirmation. Your email address will never be available publicly. 

COOKIES

The Website uses cookies to store visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, customize Website content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends. Cookies may also be used by third-party services, such as Google Analytics, as described herein.

Users may, at any time, prevent the setting of cookies, by the Website, by using a corresponding setting of your internet browser and may thus permanently deny the setting of cookies. Furthermore, already set cookies may be deleted at any time via an Internet browser or other software programs. This is possible in all popular Internet browsers. However, if users deactivate the setting of cookies in your Internet browser, not all functions of our Website may be entirely usable.

ADVERTISING

**Display Ads**

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve content and advertisements when you visit the Website, which may use cookies, as noted above.

**Retargeting Ads**

From time to time, the Website may engage in remarketing efforts with third-party companies, such as Google, Facebook, or Instagram, in order to market the Website. These companies use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Website.

**Affiliate Program Participation**

The Website may engage in affiliate marketing, which is done by embedding tracking links into the Website. If you click on a link for an affiliate partnership, a cookie will be placed on your browser to track any sales for purposes of commissions.

MidgetMomma.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and links to Amazon.com. As part of this Amazon Associates program, the Website will post customized links, provided by Amazon, to track the referrals to their website. This program utilizes cookies to track visits for the purposes of assigning commission on these sales.

Newsletters

On the Website, you may subscribe to our newsletter, which may be used for advertising purposes. All newsletters sent may contain tracking pixels. The pixel is embedded in emails and allows an analysis of the success of online marketing campaigns. Because of these tracking pixels, we may see if and when you open an email and which links within the email you click. Also, this allows the Website to adapt the content of future newsletters to the interests of the user. This behavior will not be passed on to third parties.

RIGHTS RELATED TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Opt-out – You may opt-out of future email communications by following the unsubscribe links in our emails. You may also notify us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) to be removed from our mailing list.

Access – You may access the personal information we have about you by submitting a request to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Amend – You may contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) to amend or update your personal information.

Forget – In certain situations, you may request that we erase or forget your personal data. To do so, please submit a request to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes or to complete transactions, or when required by law.

SENSITIVE PERSONAL INFORMATION

At no time should you submit sensitive personal information to the Website. This includes your social security number, information regarding race or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious beliefs, health information, criminal background, or trade union memberships. If you elect to submit such information to us, it will be subject to this Privacy Policy.

CHILDREN’S INFORMATION

The Website does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 16. If a parent or guardian believes that the Website has personally identifiable information of a child under the age of 16 in its database, please contact us immediately at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

CONTACT INFORMATION

At any time, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) for questions related to this Privacy Policy. 

**Terms of Service:**

This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation. We are happy to share information with you, that may include us being compensated for sharing that information with you. There are times that it may not say that we are being compensated for a deal like a coupon or freebie or a sponsored post. There are times that a deal I share with you, I am compensated for by an affiliate program, this does not in any way affect my opinion of it being a good deal or not. I will not share deals with you that I believe are not good deals that I would not think about purchasing for myself, my family or someone that I know.

This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. We believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity. The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content.

The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.  
To get your own policy, go to [http://www.disclosurepolicy.org](http://www.disclosurepolicy.org/)

**Our Disclaimer:  **

We at MidgetMomma.com do not guarantee the availability of the deals that we post. Not all deals are always in every location. We can not guarantee that when you sign up for a deal or freebie in the mail that you will receive it. We are only passing information on to you and we are not responsible for any information other then what is posted on this site. At no point are responsible for anything other then our opinions. We are not liable for the following, loss of business due to a review we do or anything that we state about a company, product or person. We are not liable for any incidental, consequential or indirect damages to any person, business including but not limited to, loss of profit, loss of information,or anything that comes from using our services or reading our content. Any pictures that are sent in to us become our property and we have the right to use them in whatever way we feel is more beneficial.

**Terms of Use:**

By visiting this site you are agreeing to the following but not limited to, you assume the risks of using our site and the internet. Any damages to you, your computer or anything else from clicking an external link on this site is at the users own risk, we will not be held responsible for any of it. Just because an external link is on Luxury Living Frugal Style does not mean that we approve, endorse, or guarantee the products, information or availability of anything. We make no guarantee that deals will still be available when a visitor goes to get the deal. We have no control over other sites including those that we have external links to. Visiting this other sites is at the risk of the user. By visiting Luxury Living Frugal Style you are agreeing that we hold no responsibility what so ever to anything, if you are a company who we do a review for you are accepting that our reviews are honest and we are not responsible for any loss of income, any damages that may come to you or your company and you are agree that you can not take any actions against us. You are agreeing that we have the right to publish a review if we choose to and that it will be honest and that if we choose not to post the review then it is our choice and you can not take any actions against us.

MidgetMomma.com owned  by Lauren Happel is licensed under a [Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 3.0 Unported License](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/3.0/).

Based on a work at [www.midgetmomm.com](https://www.midgetmomma.com/policies/).

Permissions beyond the scope of this license may be available at [www.midgetmomma.com](https://www.midgetmomma.com/policies/).
